[Music]
it's never easy but I'm determined to
show my family that I'm always gonna be
there for them during his last moments
he told me to never give up there is no
such thing as work/life balance
there is only work-life choices
sometimes it feels really overwhelming
[Music]
these are the tough choices that you
have to make each and every day I found
a greater purpose in life to help others
just like how he would as a father I
believe no matter how hard life gets we
have to grow stronger as a wife I've
learned that happiness comes from making
time for those you love as both a mother
and a daughter I realized that it's the
smallest moments that truly matter
I'm tabatha I'm not just here for my
family I stand by yours too I'm Mansi I
not only care for my loved ones I care
for yours too I'm Melvin I'm not just my
family's pillar of strength I'm here for
you too
[Music]